class Questions {

  Questions();

  static List<Map> questions = [
    {
      "question": "An edible oval nut with a hard shell, or the tree that it grows on.",
      "answer": "Almond",
      "choices": ["Almond", "Along", "Alone", "Aloud"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Having a strong feeling against someone who has behaved badly, making you want to shout at them or hurt them.",
      "answer": "Angry",
      "choices": ["Angry", "Angina", "Angle", "Anglo"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Something that lives and moves but is not a human, bird, fish, or insect.",
      "answer": "Animal",
      "choices": ["Animal", "Anima", "Animate", "Animus"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round fruit with firm, white flesh, and green, red, or yellow skin.",
      "answer": "Apple",
      "choices": ["Apple", "Applause", "Applaud", "Application"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Any object in the shape of a sphere, especially one used as a toy by children or in various sports such as tennis and football.",
      "answer": "Ball",
      "choices": ["Ball", "Balk", "Bale", "Ballet"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A musical instrument, usually made of wood, with six strings and a long neck, played with the fingers or a plectrum.",
      "answer": "Guitar",
      "choices": ["Guitar", "Gear", "Gary", "Guide"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A small vehicle for traveling on water.",
      "answer": "Boat",
      "choices": ["Boat", "Boater", "Boast", "Board"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A male child or, more generally, a male of any age.",
      "answer": "Boy",
      "choices": ["Boy", "Bozo", "Boxer", "Box"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A seat for one person that has a back, usually four legs, and sometimes two arms",
      "answer": "Chair",
      "choices": ["Chair", "Chain", "Chaise", "Chalk"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A boy or girl from the time of birth until he or she is an adult or a son or daughter of any age.",
      "answer": "Child",
      "choices": ["Child", "Chime", "Chimera", "Chilly"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A place where many people live, with many houses, stores, businesses, and which is bigger than a town.",
      "answer": "City",
      "choices": ["City", "Civic", "Civil", "Citizen"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A device for measuring and showing time is usually found in or on a building and not worn by a person.",
      "answer": "Clock",
      "choices": ["Clock", "Cold", "Colg", "Clomp"]
    },
    {
      "question":"A person who you know well and who you like a lot, but who is usually not a member of your family.",
      "answer":"Friend",
      "choices": ["Friend", "Friction", "Friction", "Friar"]
    },
     {
      "question":"A small animal that has smooth skin, lives in water and on land, has long powerful back legs with which it jumps from place to place.",
      "answer":"Frog",
      "choices": ["Frog","Fro","Frond" ,"From"]
    },
      {
      "question":"A flat surface, usually supported by four legs, is used for putting things on",
      "answer":"Table",
      "choices": ["Table","Tab","Tabby ","Tabor"]
    },
        {
      "question":"A tropical plant that has a root that is cooked and eaten.",
      "answer":"Taro",
      "choices": ["Taro","Tart","Tarot ","Task"]
    },
        {
      "question":"A shelter made of canvas or similar material and supported by poles and ropes, that you can fold up and carry with you.",
      "answer":"Tent",
      "choices": ["Tent","Tenth","Tepee","Tepid"]
    }
  ];

}